Hall, Kermit; Papers ua902.070
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- UAlbany Talks and Presentations, 2004-2006; 4; 2.1 cubic ft.
  - Governor D. Walker Forum on Higher Education & Economic Development, 2004 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Great Dane Awards, 2006 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Groundbreaking for Lacrosse & Field Hockey Venues, 2005 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Heart of Harriet Miers Commentary, 2005 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - High School Achievers of Color Luncheon, 2005 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Honors College Press Conference, 2005 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Introduction of Immaculee Ilibagiza Rwanda Summer Study Program, 2006 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Inaugural Albany Symposium on Crime & Justice-Welcome, 2005 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Initiatives for Women Celebration, 2005 July 21 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Initiatives for Women Reception, 2005 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Innovations and Opportunities Telecommunications-Special Guest: Senator Hillary Rodham Clinton, 2006 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Institutional Assessment Plan Compact Planning, 2005 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - International Chipmaking Venture Announced for University's Albany NanoTech, 2005 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Internationalizing the Campus (Utah), 2004 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Introduction to Recruitment & Selection Video, 2005 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Jiangsu Study Visit Dinner, 2006 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Jiangsu Study Visit Opening Dinner, 2006 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - John E. Burton Lecture & Distinguished Public Service Awards Ceremony, 2005 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Just for the Kids-New York, 2005 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Kidder, Tracy (Luncheon with Tracy Kidder), Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Launch of College of Computing & Information, 2005 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - League of Conservation Voters, 2005 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Legacy Alumni Reception, 2006 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Len Slade Development Dinner, 2006 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Li Lunch, 2006 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Linda Greenhouse Event, 2006 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Black History Month 27th Annual Luncheon, 2006 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Mayor's Press Conference, 2006 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Middle Earth 35th Anniversary Event, 2005 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Milne School Reunion Gala, 2005 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Minority Scholars Lunch, 2006 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Moving Forward with the East Campus, 2006 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - National Death Penalty Archives Event, 2005 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Nano & MBA Joint Master's Program, 2005 October 5 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - A New Look at the Institutional Component of Higher Education Finance-Overheads, Undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - The New York Court of Appeals Lecture Series "NY Times vs Sullivan and it's Times", 2006 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Northeast Regional Forensic Institute Grand Opening, 2006 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NY Biotechnology Association-UAlbany Life Sciences Forum, 2005 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NY Wired Digital Youth Graduation Ceremony, 2005 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NY Wired for Education/Times Union Conference, 2005 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NYPA Announcement on East Campus, 2005 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pancake Breakfast for Health Care Workers, 2005 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Persico Papers, 2006 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation Ceremony, 2005 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Philip Schuyler Parent Resource Center/Time Dollar Store PowerPoint Presentation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - PowerPoint Presentation: China Trip, 2005 (A/v box 1, Cd 1)
  - Presentation of Katrina Donations, 2005 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Lecture Series-"Open Secrets: The Kennedy Assassination & It's Lessons Today", 2006 April 11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Scholars Visit Day, 2005 March 9 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Presidential Scholars Visit Day Welcome, 2005 February 16 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - President's Awards for Leadership, 2006 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - President's Awards for Leadership Ceremony, 2005 March 6 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - President's Club Reception, 2006 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - President's Retreat-Overheads, 2005 April 19 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - President's Retreat-Reorganization of the University Administration & Planning Processes, 2005 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Reinventing Retirement Through Capstone Careers-PowerPoint Presentation, 2005 August (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Research Foundation Recognition Dinner, 2005 November 3 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Research University in SUNY System Jiangsu Province University President's Visit, 2006 June 13 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Researching New York Luncheon, 2005 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - School of Business Ceremony, 2006 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Siena College/UAlbany Army ROTC Overview, 2005 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Snyder, Norman Gift for School of Business, 2005 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Special Olympics Opening Ceremonies, 2006 June 15 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - School of Business Gift (Bob Lazar), 2005 October 11 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Spring Judicial College/Judicial Council Meeting Supreme Court of Arkansas, 2005 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Spring Report to the Faculty, 2005 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Spring Faculty Meeting, 2006 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Student Voices Panel-Destination Diploma III, 2005 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Sunset Hors D'oeuvres River Cruise, 2005 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Testimony by President Kermit L. Hall Before the NYS Senate & Assembly Committees on Higher Education, 2005 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Thompson, Frank Reception, 2005 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - TIAA-CREF Institute 2005 Conference, 2005 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Torch Night, 2006 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Twenty-Two Keys to Constitutions & Rights in American History-League of Women Voters, 2005 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - UAlbany Alums Overhead, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - UAlbany Division for Research 6th Annual Research Colloquium, 2005 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - UAlbany Foundation Board Reception, 2006 June 15 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - UAlbany Foundation-East Campus Steering Committee, 2005 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - UAS Board Meeting, 2005 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - University at Albany: Neighbor, Partner, Ally Pine Hills Neighborhood Association, 2005 December 5 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - University at Albany: Neighbor, Partner, Ally Presentation to Albany Roundtable, 2005 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - University Art Museum Opening Reception-"New Emerging from the Old Lu Shengzhong Works", 2005 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - University Design: Principles for the Future Whiteman Osterman Hanna Breakfast Forum, Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - University Medallion Presentation to Dr. Carol Gilligan, 2006 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - UPD Annual Awards Ceremony for '04 Staff Performance, 2005 March 24 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Videoconference with Ohio State University & Virtual Ribbon-Cutting, 2005 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Voice of the Parent Panel, 2005 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Welcome Candlelighting Ceremony, 2005 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Welcome Dinner for International Students, 2005 August 24 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Wendell Lorang Retirement Reception, 2006 April 20 (Box 2, Folder 54)